Guide to the Media Services Audio and Video Recordings, 1963 - ongoing
Duke University. University Archives
Media Services Audio and Video Recordings, 1963 - ongoing.
Duke University. Auxiliary Services. Media Services.
31 linear feet, Extent: 514 Items
Duke University. University Archives
Media Services (also referred to as Duke Studios) provides broadcast quality media production services to all parts of the Duke University community. Its services include video and audio production and post-production (including event documentation), project design, production equipment rentals, tape duplication, custom CDs and DVDs, and computer graphics and animation. Collection includes audio and video recordings of campus events, programming produced for various university offices and departments, and musical recordings. Campus events include basketball, football, the inaugurations of presidents Richard Brodhead, Keith Brodie, and Nannerl Keohane, dedication of the Doris Duke Memorial, the retirement and funeral of Terry Sanford, events related to September 11, 2001, a remembrance of Benjamin N. Duke, and commencement ceremonies. Authors, scholars, and other notable people represented include John Hope Franklin, Jesse Jackson, Reynolds Price, Ronald Reagan, Elie Wiesel, Billy Graham, C. D. Wright, Gerald Barrax, Elizabeth Cox, Tim McLaurin, Eric Meyers, Orrin Pilkey, and Alex Roland. Musical recordings include the Duke University Concert Band, Dan Locklair, and 1980s rock band the X-Teens.
UA.10.03.0003
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48 hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Use of audiotapes and videotapes from this collection requires the creation of reference copies. Reference copies for some of the tapes have been made, and if a reference copy exists, it is noted in this finding aid. To arrange for the creation of reference copies of other items, please contact University Archives staff. Although these recordings are now stored in a stable environment, their condition and playback quality is unknown.
Provenance
The Media Services Audio and Video Recordings was received by the University Archives as transfers in 1989-2014, accession numbers UA89-0059, UA93-144, UA94-136, UA96-115, UA97-6, UA97-57, UA2003-20, UA2003-23, UA2005-14, UA2005-45, UA2009-0026, UA2009-0035, UA2011-0007, and UA2014-0018.
Historical Note
Media Services (also referred to as Duke Studios) provides broadcast quality media production services to all parts of the Duke University community. Duke Studios was established in 1980 as an audio production facility in the Biddle Building on East Campus. In 1989, it moved to the Bryan Center on West Campus. It has expanded its services to include video and audio production and post-production (including event documentation), project design, production equipment rentals, tape duplication, custom CDs and DVDs, and computer graphics and animation.
Media Services was formerly known as Technical Services and was a division of Auxiliary Services. Media Services and Technical Services later became two separate departments within Event Management, a Division of Auxiliary Services. Technical Services provides technical support services including audio-visual rentals, sound reinforcement, and audio-visual maintenance and support in many campus facilities. Technical Services assists departments and student organizations throughout the Duke campus including Duke Athletics, academic classes and meetings, student organized bands and speakers, and sound systems for University-wide events such as Graduation and Convocation.
Collection Overview
Collection includes audio and video recordings of campus events, programming produced for various university offices and departments, and musical recordings. Campus events include basketball, football, the inaugurations of presidents Richard Brodhead, Keith Brodie, and Nannerl Keohane, dedication of the Doris Duke Memorial, the retirement and funeral of Terry Sanford, events related to September 11, 2001, a remembrance of Benjamin N. Duke, and commencement ceremonies. Authors, scholars, and other notable people represented include John Hope Franklin, Jesse Jackson, Reynolds Price, Ronald Reagan, Elie Wiesel, Billy Graham, C. D. Wright, Gerald Barrax, Elizabeth Cox, Tim McLaurin, Eric Meyers, Orrin Pilkey, and Alex Roland. Musical recordings include the Duke University Concert Band, Dan Locklair, and 1980s rock band the X-Teens.
Subject Headings
Barrax, Gerald W.; Brodhead, Richard; Brodie, H. Keith H. (Harlow Keith Hammond), 1939-; Cox, Elizabeth, 1942-; Duke University. Auxiliary Services. Media Services; Duke University. Auxiliary Services. Technical Services; Duke University -- Basketball; Duke University -- Commencement ceremonies; Duke University. Duke Studios; Duke University. Concert Band; Duke University -- Football; Franklin, John Hope, 1915-; Keohane, Nannerl O., 1940-; Locklair, Dan; McLaurin, Tim; Meyers, Eric M.; Pilkey, Orrin H., 1934-; Price, Reynolds, 1933-; Roland, Alex, 1944-; Sanford, Terry, 1917-; September 11 Terrorist Attacks, 2001 -- Social aspects; Wiesel, Elie, 1928-; Wright, C. D., 1949-; X-Teens (Musical group); Sound recordings; Video recordings
Contents of Collection
- Video Recordings, 1980-2005, undated
  - Athletics, 1985-2001, undated (Box 1)
    Arranged alphabetically by sport and then chronologically.
    - Athletic Complex Naming Gift Presentation, 1997 Jan. 11, 2 videocassettes (betacam SP) (Box 1)
    - Basketball: Basketball Team Returns, 1988 Apr. 5, 2 videocassettes (U-matic) (Box 1)
    - Basketball: Basketball Team Returns, 1989 Apr. 4, 1 videocassette (U-matic) (Box 1)
    - Basketball: Duke vs. Cornell, 1988 Dec. 29, 1 videocassette (U-matic) (Box 1)
    - Basketball: Duke Basketball Retrospective, circa 1985-1990, 1 videocassette (VHS) (Box 1)
    - Football: Wake Forest, 1987 Jan. 21, 1 videocassette (U-matic) (Box 1)
    - Football: Coca-Cola Bowl, 1991 Dec. 1, 4 videocassettes (betacam) (Box 1)
    - Football $5 Million, undated, 1 videocassette (betacam SP) (Box 1)
    - Golf: 2001 NCAA Golf Championships, 2001 Apr. 9, 1 videocassette (MiniDV) (Box 1)
  - Campus Events, 1980-2005, undated (Box 1)
    Arranged alphabetically by subject or title.
    - Richard Brodhead: New President, 2003 Dec. 12, 1 videocassette (DVCAM) (Box 1)
    - Richard Brodhead, Nannerl Keohane, Judy Woodruff: A Conversation in One Brief Afternoon, 2004 Feb. 1, 1 videodisc (DVD)/1 VHS master (UA2009-0026) (Box 1)
    - Richard Brodhead: Inauguration Concert, 2004 Sept. 14, 1 videocassette (DVCAM) (Box 1)
    - Richard Brodhead: Inauguration Concert Program, 2004 Sept. 14 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Richard Brodhead Inauguration: Faculty Luncheon, Pratt Commons, 2004 Sept. 17, 1 videocassette (DVCAM) (Box 1)
    - Richard Brodhead Inauguration: Duke Chapel, 2004 Sept. 18, 1 videocassette (betacam SP) (Box 1)
    - Richard Brodhead Inauguration: Duke Chapel, 2004 Sept. 18, 1 videocassette (DVCAM) (Box 1)
    - H. Keith H. Brodie: Inauguration, 1985 July 1, 6 videocassettes (U-matic) (Box 2)
    - H. Keith H. Brodie: Tape 2, circa 1985, 1 videocassette (U-matic) (Box 2)
    - H. Keith H. Brodie, circa 1993-1999, 5 videocassettes (betacam SP) (Box 2)
    - Bryan Center Groundbreaking, circa 1980, 3 videocassettes (U-matic); 1 videocassette (VHS) (Box 2)
    - Campaign for Duke Press Conference, 1998 Oct. 1, 2 videocassettes (betacam SP) (Box 2)
    - Chapel Choir China Tour, 1997, 1 videocassette (VHS) (Box 2)
    - Christmas in Duke Chapel, 1998, 1 videocassette (betacam SP) (Box 3)
    - Doris Duke: Doris Duke Bequest News Conference, 1995 Mar. 29, 1 videocassette (betacam SP)
      - Reference Copy: VHS UA96-115-1 (Box 3)
    - Doris Duke: Memorial, Duke Chapel, 1996 Sept. 30, 1 videocassette (betacam SP) (Box 3)
    - Doris Duke Memorial Release Package, 1996 Sept. 10, 1 videocassette (betacam SP) (10 min.) (Box 3)
    - Doris Duke Dedication, undated, 1 videocassette (betacam SP) (Box 3)
    - Jeff and Gregg Foxworthy at Duke Hospital, 1999 Jan. 1, 1 videocassette (betacam SP) (Box 3)
    - John Hope Franklin's 80th Birthday, 1995 Jan. 19, 1 videocassette (betacam SP) (Box 3)
    - John Hope Franklin, undated, 1 videocassette (betacam SP) (Box 3)
    - Freshman Orientation, Tape 2 of 2, 1986 Aug. 28, 1 videocassette (U-matic); camera original (Box 3)
    - Jesse Jackson: Duke Chapel, 1993 Mar. 9, 2 videocassettes (betacam SP); 1 videocassette (VHS) (Box 3)
    - Installation of L. Gregory Jones as Dean of the Divinity School, 1997 Oct. 3, 1 videocassette (betacam SP) (Box 3)
    - Nannerl O. Keohane: New President, 1992 Dec. 11, 1 videocassette (betacam SP) (Box 3)
    - Nannerl O. Keohane: Inauguration, 1993 Oct. 23, camera originals; 8 videocassettes (betacam SP) (Box 4)
    - Ambitions Realized: A Nod to Nan, 2002 Oct. 3, 1 videocassette (DVCAM) (8 min.) (Box 3)
    - Nannerl O. Keohane: Founder's Day, 2003, 1 videocassette (betacam SP) (Box 3)
    - Bill King Anniversary, undated, 3 videocassettes (betacam SP) (Box 3)
    - Douglas Maitland Knight: Memorial Service, 2005 Apr. 15, 1 videocassette (betacam SP) (Box 4)
    - Library: 4 Millionth Book Ceremony, 1992 Apr. 10, 3 videocassettes (betacam SP) (Box 4)
    - Nasher Museum of Art Groundbreaking and Dinner, 2001 Dec. 6, 1 videocassette (betacam SP) (Box 4)
    - Nicholas Family Press Conference, 1995 Dec. 7, 2 videocassettes (betacam SP) (Box 4)
    - Nicholas School of the Environment Dedication, 1995, 3 videocassettes (betacam SP) (Box 4)
    - Pearsall, George W.: What is Safe?, Tape 2 of 2, 1985 June 24, 1 videocassette (U-matic) (Box 4)
    - Chuck Peseski: Mech. Eng. Experiment, Tape 2, circa 1980-1990, 1 videocassette (U-matic) (Box 5)
    - Politics of Academic Freedom, Zener Auditorium, 2004 Mar. 1, 1 videocassette (DVCAM) (Box 5)
    - Reynolds Price, 1987 Aug. 16, edit master; 1 videocassette (U-matic) (Box 5)
    - Ronald Reagan, undated, edit master; 1 videocassette (U-matic) (Box 5)
    - Terry Sanford: Retirement, 1985, 1 videocassette (U-matic) (Box 5)
    - Terry Sanford: No. 1, Cameron pre-remarks and show, circa 1985, 1 videocassette (U-matic) (Box 5)
    - Terry Sanford: Sanford Retirement Gala, no. 3 of 3, 1985, 1 videocassette (U-matic) (Box 5)
    - Terry Sanford: tent, march, opening interior, circa 1985, 1 videocassette (U-matic) (Box 5)
    - Terry Sanford Funeral: B-Roll, 1998 Apr. 21, 1 videocassette (betacam SP) (Box 5)
    - Terry Sanford Funeral: #1, 1998 Apr. 22, 1 videocassette (betacam SP) (Box 5)
    - Terry Sanford Funeral: WTVD, 1998 Apr. 22, 1 videocassette (VHS) (Box 5)
    - Terry Sanford Funeral: WUNC-TV, 1998 Apr. 22, 2 videocassettes (betacam SP) (Box 5)
    - Terry Sanford Funeral: UNC Feed from SAT Truck, 1998 Apr. 22, 1 videocassette (VHS) (Box 5)
    - Video New Releases, 1993 Nov. 4, undated, 1 videocassette (betacam SP) (Box 5)
      1. R. Thomas: Phytotron
      2. Keohane Inauguration
      3. Roses Bites and B-Roll, 1993 Nov. 4
      4. NASA Shuttle Project
    - Campus Events Related to September 11, 2001 (Box 6)
      Arranged chronologically.
      - Interfaith Prayer Vigil, Duke Chapel Quad, 2001 Sept. 12, 1 videocassette (DVCAM) (Box 6)
      - President Keohane panel on Fragmentation, 2001 Sept. 16, 1 videocassette (DVCAM); 1 videocassette (VHS) (Box 6)
      - The New War on Terrorism: Initial Assessments, Sanford Institute, 2001 Sept. 24, 1 videocassette (DVCAM) (Box 6)
      - Christianity, War, and Patriotism, York Chapel, 2001 Sept. 25, 1 videocassette (DVCAM) (Box 6)
      - Memorial Concert, Duke Chapel, 2001 Sept. 30, 1 videocassette (DVCAM); 1 videocassette (S-VHS) (Box 6)
      - Memorial Concert, Duke Chapel, Program and Flyer 2001 Sept. 30 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      - World Trade Center Disaster Forum, Law School, 2001 Oct. 2, 1 videocassette (DVCAM) (Box 6)
      - Terrorism Crisis and the World Economy: What Effects, What Strategies?, Fuqua School of Business, 2001 Oct. 8, 1 videocassette (DVCAM) (Box 6)
      - The Morality of War in Islamic and Christian Perspective, York Chapel, 2001 Oct. 9, 1 videocassette (DVCAM) (Box 6)
      - Technology for Counter Terrorism, Pratt School of Engineering, 2001 Oct. 25, 1 videocassette (DVCAM) (Box 6)
      - Joseph Lieberman: 2001 Terry Sanford Distinguished Lecturer, 2001 Oct. 28, 1 videocassette (DVCAM) (Box 6)
      - Joseph Lieberman: 2001 Terry Sanford Distinguished Lecturer Program, 2001 Oct. 28 (Box 6, Folder 3)
      - Medical Aspects of Terrorism, 2001 Nov. 26, 1 videocassette (DVCAM) (Box 6)
      - Al Jazeera Event, 2002 Feb. 27, 1 videocassette (DVCAM) (Box 6)
      - 9/11: Perspectives and Policy Implications, 2002 Sept. 11, 1 videocassette (DVCAM) (Box 6)
  - Commencement Ceremonies, 1984-2003 (Box 7)
    - Commencement, 1984 May, 1 videocassette (U-matic) (Box 7)
    - Graduation, 1986 May 4, camera originals: 3 videocassettes (U-matic) (Box 7)
    - Commencement, 1987, camera originals: 4 videocassettes (U-matic); edit masters: 2 videocassettes (U-matic) (Box 7)
    - Ted Koppel: Commencement, 1987 May 10, 1 videocassette (VHS) (Box 8)
    - Commencement, 1988 May 8, camera originals: 3 videocassettes (U-matic); camera original: 1 videocassette (VHS); edit masters: 2 videocassettes (U-matic) (Box 8)
    - Graduation, 1989, edit masters: 4 videocassettes (U-matic); 1 videocassette (VHS) (Box 8)
    - Graduation, 1990, camera originals: 3 videocassettes (U-matic) (Box 8)
    - Graduation, 1991 May 12, 3 videocassettes (U-matic) (Box 8)
    - Graduation, 1993 May 16, edit masters: 2 videocassettes (betacam SP); dub of edit master #2: 1 videocassette (betacam SP) (Box 8)
    - Graduation, 1997, camera originals: 2 videocassettes (betacam SP) (Box 8)
    - Duke University Graduation Exercises, 1997 May 18, camera originals: 5 videocassettes (betacam SP) (Box 9)
    - Duke Graduation, 1998 May 17, camera originals: 12 videocassettes (betacam SP) (Box 9)
    - Duke University Baccalaureate Service, 1999 May 14, 1 videocassette (VHS) (Box 9)
    - Duke University Baccalaureate Service, 1999 May 15, 1 videocassette (VHS) (Box 9)
    - Graduation, 1999 May 16, camera originals: 12 videocassettes (betacam SP) (Box 9)
    - Baccalaureate, 2002, 3 videocassettes (S-VHS) (Box 9)
    - Baccalaureate, 2003, 2 videocassettes (DVCAM) (Box 9)
  - Productions, 1988-1995, undated (Box 6)
    Arranged alphabetically by title.
    - Duke University Today, 1988, 1 videocassette (betacam SP) (12 min.) (Box 6)
    - Living History: Cuban Missile Crisis, undated, 1 videocassette (betacam SP) (Box 6)
      Narration: Alex Roland
    - Living History: Tribute to Angier Biddle Duke, undated, 1 videocassette (betacam SP) (16:45 min.) (Box 6)
    - Living History: Elie Wiesel, 1987 Sept. 15, camera original: 1 videocassette (U-matic) (Box 6)
    - Year at Duke: Duke Undergrad Admissions, undated, 1 videocassette (betacam SP) (28:45 min.) (Box 6)
    - Yearlook, 1995, 1 videocassette (U-matic) (Box 6)
  - Miscellaneous, 1980-1990, undated (Box 6)
    - Archive tape, undated, 1 videocassette (U-matic) (Box 6)
    - Graphics, circa 1980-1990, 1 videocassette (U-matic) (Box 6)
    - Helicopter Footage, circa 1980-1990, 2 videocassettes (U-matic) (Box 6)
    - J. Walter Thompson Photo Ad Archives B-Roll, 1995 Nov. 2, 1 videocassette (betacam SP) (Box 6)
    - Stock Footage: Gardens, circa 1980-1990, 1 videocassette (U-matic) (Box 6)
    - Stock Footage: West Campus, 1984 Nov. 10, 1 videocassette (U-matic) (Box 6)
- Audio Recordings, 1963-2000, undated
  - Campus Events, 1980-1991 (Box 10)
    - Preservation Hall Jazz Band, Page Auditorium, 1977 Feb. 4., 1 sound cassette (Box 10)
    - Livingston/Rutgers Jazz with Dizzy Gillespie, Page Auditorium, 1980 Summer, 1 sound cassette (Box 10)
    - Fiftieth Anniversary Celebration, Duke University Chapel, 1980 Oct. 22, 1 sound tape reel: 10 in. (Box 10)
    - Fiftieth Anniversary Celebration Program, 1980 Oct. 22 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Archibald Cox Address to Duke Law School Class of 1981, 1 sound cassette (Box 10)
    - Billy Graham, Duke University Chapel, 1985 Nov. 17, 1 sound tape reel: 10 in. (Box 10)
    - Service of Worship Program, 1985 Nov. 17 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Alumni Admissions Forum, 1990 July 13, 7 sound cassettes (Box 10)
    - Alumni Admissions Forum Program, 1990 July 13 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Basketball: Duke Basketball Team Returns, NCAA Champs, 1991 April 2, 1 sound cassette (DAT) (Box 10)
  - Productions, 1978-2000, undated (Box 11)
    Arranged alphabetically by title or subject.
    - The Awakening, 1978 July 23, 2 sound tape reels: 7 in. (Box 11)
    - Benefits: Duke University Benefits Program, 1990 Nov. 15, 1 sound tape reel: 10 in. (Box 10)
    - Benefits, 1994 Jan. 28, 1 sound tape reel: 10 in. (Box 10)
    - Benefits: Phylis Profer, 1994 Dec., 1 sound tape reel: 10 in. (Box 10)
    - Benefits Orientation Slide Show Narration, 1995 May 22, 1 sound cassette (DAT) (Box 10)
    - Benefits: Phylis Profer, 1995 Oct. 23, 1 sound tape reel: 10 in. (Box 10)
    - Benefits, undated, 1 sound tape reel: 10 in. (Box 10)
    - Benefits: Duke Biweekly Employee Benefits, undated, 2 sound tape reels: 7 in. (Box 11)
    - H. Keith H. Brodie: Orientation, undated, 1 sound tape reel: 7 in. (Box 11)
    - Bryan Center Slide Show, undated, 1 sound tape reel: 7 in. (Box 11)
    - Carillon: Pre-Repair Reference Recording, 1992 May 14, Post Repair, 1992 Oct. 26, 1 sound cassette (DAT) (Box 10)
    - Chamber of Commerce: Durham, City of Medicine, 1983 Feb., 2 sound tape reels: 7 in. (Box 11)
    - Cheerleaders, 1989 Aug. 10, 1 sound tape reel: 7 in. (Box 11)
    - Children's Classic, 1979, 2 sound cassettes (Box 10)
      Archie Campbell, Tom Sullivan, Woody Woodbury, P. Hayes, M. Healy, Forrest Tucker, A. Freeman, Eubie Blake, Professor Irwin Corey, Perry Como
    - Choriocarcinoma Slide Show, undated, 1 sound tape reel: 7 in. (Box 11)
    - Class of '39, undated, 2 sound tape reels: 10 in. (Box 11)
    - Davison Society, 1979, 2 sound cassettes (Box 10)
    - Benjamin N. Duke: Celebration of the Life of Benjamin N. Duke, 1979 Feb. 22, 1 sound tape reel: 7 in. (Box 11)
    - Benjamin N. Duke: Remembering Ben Duke, undated, 1 sound cassette; duplication master: 2 sound tape reels: 7 in. (Box 11)
    - Cornelius Eady, 1994 May 19, 1 sound tape reel: 10 in. (Box 10)
    - Earbook, 1981, 5 sound tape reels: 7 in. (Box 11)
    - Earbook, 1981, 1 sound tape reel: 10 in.; 1 sound tape reel: 10 in., 1 in. tape (Box 10)
    - Fall Dance, 1985, 1 sound tape reel: 7 in. (Box 11)
    - John Hope Franklin: My Recent Visit to Xanadu, 1998 Sept. 30, 1 sound cassette (DAT) (Box 10)
    - Freshman Orientation Slide Show, 1983 Jan., 1 sound tape reel: 7 in. (Box 11)
    - Gifts to Endowments: Taking Life Insurance out of the Closet, undated, 1 sound tape reel: 7 in. (Box 11)
    - Hospital Fire Safety Slide Show, undated, 1 sound tape reel: 7 in. (Box 11)
    - Hospital Public Relations Radio Spots, undated, 1 sound tape reel: 7 in. (Box 11)
    - KKG Show, undated, 1 sound tape reel: 7 in. (Box 11)
    - Vic Lukas: Orientation, 1982, 2 sound tape reels: 7 in. (Box 11)
    - Lutheran Campus Ministry, 1982 May, 2 sound tape reels: 7 in. (Box 11)
    - Nursing School History Slide Show, undated, 1 sound tape reel: 10 in. (Box 10)
    - PBC Live: Cotton, undated, 1 sound tape reel: 10 in. (Box 12)
    - Personal Hygiene and Dress Code, 1982 Aug., 1 sound tape reel: 7 in. (Box 12)
    - Poison Control Center Slide Show, 1982 Mar., 2 sound tape reels: 7 in. (Box 12)
    - Reynolds Price: Master Takes NPR, 1995, 1 sound cassette (DAT) (Box 10)
    - Reynolds Price: Acoustiguide, 1996 Oct. 8, 1 sound cassette (DAT) (Box 10)
    - Reynolds Price: The Gospel According to Mark, 2000 Apr. 17, 1 sound cassette (DAT) (Box 10)
    - Public Relations: Civitan Appeal, undated, 1 sound tape reel: 7 in. (Box 11)
    - Michael Rush Project: Le Cirque du Temps, 1990, 4 sound tape reels: 7 in. (Box 11)
    - Marjorie Scheer: The Occupation, undated, 1 sound tape reel: 7 in. (Box 13)
    - Marjorie Scheer: The Wavering, undated, 1 sound tape reel: 7 in. (Box 13)
    - School of Forestry Slide Show, 1986-1987, 4 sound tape reels: 7 in. (Box 13)
    - State Employees Credit Union: Assembly Master, 1980 May, 1 sound tape reel: 7 in. (Box 13)
    - State Employees Credit Union: Mixdown Master, 1980 May, 1 sound tape reel: 7 in. (Box 13)
    - Structure House Introduction: Dr. Gerard J. Musante, 1995 Sept. 29, 1 sound cassette (DAT) (Box 12)
    - Structure House Master, 1997 June 24, 1 sound cassette (DAT) (Box 12)
    - Student Labor Slide Show: Assembly Master, 1982 Nov., 1 sound tape reel: 7 in. (Box 13)
    - Student Labor Slide Show: Final Mix, 1982 Nov., 1 sound tape reel: 7 in. (Box 13)
    - Talking Books: C. D. Wright, 1994 Oct. 21, 1 sound cassette (DAT) (Box 12)
    - Talking Books: Gerald Barrax, 1993 June 25, 1 sound tape reel: 10 in. (Box 12)
    - Talking Books: Elizabeth Cox, 1993, 2 sound tape reels: 10 in. (Box 12)
    - Talking Books: Tim McLaurin, 1993, 2 sound tape reels: 10 in. (Box 12)
    - What Makes Duke so Special, 1988 Nov. 12, 2 sound tape reels: 7 in. (Box 13)
    - Nathan Womack Interview, 1971 Dec. 9, 2 sound tape reels: 7 in. (Box 13)
    - Alumni Lecture Series, 1986-1988, undated (Box 12)
      Arranged alphabetically by speaker's last name.
      - Charlie Braswell Intros, undated, 1 sound tape reel: 7 in. (Box 12)
      - Keith Brodie Intros, 1987 Sept. 14, 1 sound tape reel: 7 in. (Box 12)
      - Lee Iacocca: Commencement Address, 1986, 1 sound tape reel (25 min., 16 sec.): 7 in. (Box 12)
      - Lee Iacocca / Ted Koppel: Commencement Address, 1986and 1987, 1 sound cassette
        - reference copy: UA2003-23-1 (Box 12)
      - Ted Koppel: Commencement Address, 1987, 1 sound tape reel (18 min., 25 sec.): 7 in. (Box 12)
      - Eric Meyers, undated, 1 sound tape reel (45 min., 20 sec.): 10 in. (Box 12)
      - Eric Meyers: Judaism and Christianity, 1988, 1 sound cassette
        - reference copy: UA2003-23-2 (Box 12)
      - Orrin Pilkey, undated, 1 sound tape reel (42 min., 23 sec.): 10 in. (Box 12)
      - Orrin Pilkey: The Changing Seashore, 1988, 1 sound cassette
        - reference copy: UA2003-23-3 (Box 12)
      - Reynolds Price, undated, 1 sound tape reel (56 min., 21 sec.): 10 in. (Box 12)
      - Reynolds Price: Selected Readings, undated, 1 sound cassette
        - reference copy: UA2003-23-4 (Box 12)
      - Alex Roland, undated, 1 sound tape reel (52 min., 40 sec.): 10 in. (Box 12)
      - Alex Roland: The Manned Space Program, 1988, 1 sound cassette
        - reference copy: UA2003-23-5 (Box 12)
      - Alumni Tape, Side A, undated, 1 sound tape reel: 7 in. (Box 12)
      - Alumni Tape, Side B, undated, 1 sound tape reel: 10 in. (Box 12)
  - Musical Recordings, 1963-1990, undated (Box 14)
    Arranged alphabetically by artist's name.
    - Linz Audain: piano/voice demo, undated, 1 sound tape reel: 10 in. (Box 14)
    - Michael Ching: Durham, undated, 1 sound tape reel: 10 in.; 1 sound tape reel: 10 in., 1 in. tape (Box 14)
    - Duke University Concert Band, 1963 Apr. 15, 1 sound tape reel: 10 in. (Box 15)
    - Duke University Concert Band, 1964 Apr. 15, 2 sound tape reels: 10 in. (Box 15)
    - Duke University Concert Band, 1964 Apr. 16, 1 sound tape reel: 10 in. (Box 15)
    - Duke University Concert Band, 1964 Dec. 13, 1 sound tape reel: 10 in. (Box 15)
    - Duke University Concert Band, 1964 Dec., 2 sound tape reels: 10 in. (Box 15)
    - Duke University Concert Band, circa 1964, 2 sound tape reels: 10 in. (Box 15)
    - Duke University Symphony, 1965 Mar. 18, 2 sound tape reels: 10 in. (Box 15)